A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9 FA1721
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), 1997-2006; 9; 52.57 Cubic Feet
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 27664-27699 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 27664-27699 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 27664-27699 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5100-5214 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5100-5214 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5100-5214 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5215-5401 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5215-5401 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5215-5401 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5403-5499 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5403-5499 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5403-5499 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5500-5644 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5500-5644 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5500-5644 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5645-5761 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5645-5761 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5645-5761 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5762-5864 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5762-5864 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5762-5864 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5865-6048 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5865-6048 (Box 8)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5865-6048 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 6050-6208 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 6050-6208 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 6050-6208 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 6209-6996 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 6209-6996 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 6209-6996 (Box 9)
  - The Cleveland Clinic Foundation, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 111378 (Box 9)
  - The Cleveland Clinic Foundation, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 111378 (Box 9)
  - The Cleveland Clinic Foundation, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 111378 (Box 9)
  - The Cleveland Clinic Foundation, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 111378 (Box 9)
  - The Cleveland Clinic Foundation, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 111378 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 20924-24676 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 20924-24676 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 20924-24676 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25154-25863 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 25154-25863 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 25154-25863 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25864-25990 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 25864-25990 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 25864-25990 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25992-26077 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 25992-26077 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 25992-26077 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 26245-27597 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 26245-27597 (Box 9)
  - Community, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 26245-27597 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101684-101715 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101684-101715 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center,Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101684-101715 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101684-101715 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101684-101715 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101716-101746 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101716-101746 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101716-101746 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101716-101746 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101716-101746 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101747-101777 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101747-101777 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101747-101777 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101747-101777 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101747-101777 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101778-101807 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101778-101807 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101778-101807 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101778-101807 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101778-101807 (Box 9)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101808-101839 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101808-101839 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101808-101839 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101808-101839 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101808-101839 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101840-101883 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101840-101883 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101840-101883 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101840-101883 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101840-101883 (Box 10)
  - Charleston, Covenant Health Loudon, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1 (Box 10)
  - Charleston, Covenant Health Loudon, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2 (Box 10)
  - Charleston, Covenant Health Loudon, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3 (Box 10)
  - Charleston, Covenant Health Loudon, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4 (Box 10)
  - Charleston, Covenant Health Loudon, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5 (Box 10)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4 (Box 11)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3 (Box 11)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2 (Box 11)
  - Charleston Area Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 104137-104938 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 104137-104938 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 104137-104933 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 104137-105000 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 104137-104940 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 10520-105299 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 10520-105300 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 10520-105299 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 10520-105300 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 10520-105300 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 106437-106798 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 106437-106999 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 106437-106999 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 106437-106999 (Box 11)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 106437-106999 (Box 12)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 107000-108000 (Box 12)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 107000-108000 (Box 12)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 107000-108000 (Box 12)
  - Covenant Health Park - West - Crozer Chester, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 107000-108000 (Box 12)
  - Rush North Shore Medical Center Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 13)
  - Rush North Shore Medical Center Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 13)
  - Rush North Shore Medical Center Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 13)
  - Rush North Shore Medical Center Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 13)
  - Rush North Shore Medical Center Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page5 (Box 13)
  - Spectrum Hospital, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1 (Box 13)
  - Spectrum Hospital, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2 (Box 13)
  - Spectrum Hospital, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3 (Box 13)
  - Spectrum Hospital, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4 (Box 13)
  - Spectrum Hospital, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 13)
  - St. Charles General Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1 (Box 13)
  - St. Charles General Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2 (Box 13)
  - St. Charles General Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3 (Box 13)
  - St. Charles General Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4 (Box 13)
  - St. Charles General Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5 (Box 13)
  - Suburban Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1 (Box 13)
  - Suburban Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2 (Box 13)
  - Suburban Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3 (Box 13)
  - Suburban Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4 (Box 14)
  - Suburban Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 23501-23699 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 23501-23699 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 23501-23699 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 23700-27205 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 23700-27205 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 23700-27205 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 237208-27578 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 237208-27578 (Box 14)
  - Summit, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 237208-27578 (Box 14)
  - Sunrise, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 20065-27503 (Box 14)
  - Sunrise, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 20065-27503 (Box 14)
  - Sunrise, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 20065-27503 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 105857-105910 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 105911-105973 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 105974-106049 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 106050-106117 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 106118-106233 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 105857-105910 (Box 14)